enterthemeeting.com 2017-06-06

# MeetingBurner® -

Your privacy is very important to us, and we will treat your data with care and respect. We know that you care how information and data about you is collected, used and shared. This Privacy Statement describes our privacy policy and details how we collect, use, and/or disseminate the information you provide. We reserve the right change this Statement at any time and urge you to review our Statement regularly to familiarize yourself with any changes.

**By visiting our website, using our online products/services, downloading/installing and/or using our application on a mobile phone, and/or by voluntarily submitting information to us via online forms, advertisement responses, mobile applications, and/or electronic mail, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.  
**   
**Who We Are**  
MeetingBurner has developed and licenses a subscription-based service that allows a host/presenter to share the contents of his computer monitor, his video camera, and his voice with other participants. All of this is conducted via the internet and/or with our optional phone bridge add-on. The host can configure his account so that participants can see a logo, a picture of the presenter, meeting information, participant lists, or other information as the host/presenter chooses. In addition, we allow the participants to ask electronic questions of the host. Due to the fact that each online meeting is controlled by an independent host/presenter, we cannot guarantee how the system and privacy information will be managed by the independent host/presenter.  
Individual presenters/hosts using the MeetingBurner System are referred to as “hosts". The host’s targeted audience is a “participant.” “Users” or “You” includes hosts and/or participants, as well as anyone visiting a site or application hosted by MeetingBurner.

To cater to users of our site, we may be required to collect, use, and share certain information. The type of information we collect, together with a description of how we use and/or share it, is described below

**Information Collection**  
MeetingBurner, our partners, and the hosts who use MeetingBurner are the owners of the information collected on Meeetingburner.com. 

**Registration**  
In order to use MeetingBurner, a user may first be required to complete a registration form. During registration, a user may be required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We may use this information to contact you about services on our site for which you have expressed interest. If a user chose to use our service, in certain circumstances the law may require us to collect your social security number or if a company, their EIN number. These numbers will be collected only if they are required to comply with IRS requirements.

A host registering for a pro or premier account with MeetingBurner will also be required to provide financial information (such as a credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill a host’s order. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the host.

**Information Use**  
We will use personal information that we gather about you to provide the services you have requested. In addition, if you have a free account with MeetingBurner, then we will use the information gathered about you to share more information about our business in an attempt to convince you to make a purchase from us or our associated companies. MeetingBurner and, if you are a participant in an online meeting or webinar, the host who sent you to this site, will be granted access to your personal contact (name, phone number, and email) information so that they may communicate with you in an attempt to "sell" various products, services, and memberships to you.

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users' personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do share your profile with other third parties. Your profile is shared together with your personally identifiable information. YOUR CREDIT CARD, SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER OR EIN, AND OTHER PRIVATE FINANCIAL INFORMATION IS NEVER SHARED WITH ANY OUTSIDE THIRD PARTY UNLESS REQUIRED BY LAW OR FOR BILLING PURPOSES.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer (defined to include all computing devices, including tablets, pcs, smartphones, smartwatches, and any other device that can be used to operate our software) tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the 'Profile' section.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are only tied to personally identifiable information provided by you when necessary to enable our Web-based service.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons, Web Bugs, CSS, and similar functionality)**  
We may employ or our third party advertising company(ies) may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are tied to users' personally identifiable information.

Clear Gifs can "work with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same Web site or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited 'www.companyX.com', which uses an advertising company's clear gif, the Web site or advertising company would match the clear gif's identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information would then be given to the advertising company or Web site.

In addition, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section. 

**Retargeting**  
MeetingBurner and/or its hosts may also use 3rd party vendor remarketing tracking pixels, or cookies. This means we may continue to show ads to you across the internet. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number.  
We are able to do this by placing advertising cookies on your computer as you browse our site, so that we can understand what you are interested in. One of our advertising partners may then use this information to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with MeetingBurner.  
You may be able to opt out of targeted advertising through your browser’s “settings” tab or by visiting the sites of the various remarketing vendors. You will still receive just as many advertisements, just not those relevant to you.

## Communications from the Site

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new users a welcome email. Established users may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Customer Service**  
We also communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account. We reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users’ wishes.

**Sharing With Third Parties**  
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Third-Party Advertisers/Parties**  
We may use the personal contact information you have voluntarily provided to us to cause information, offers, products, and/or services that appear to us to be consistent with your expressed interests to be directed to you. This is typically accomplished by using your information to direct to you information, offers, products, and/or services from us and/or one of our affiliated companies. Your information may, therefore, ultimately be used for marketing purposes by us, our affiliated companies, any one or more the associated businesses with which we work, and/or the host of a meeting.   
Please be aware that after we share your information with the host of a meeting, our affiliated companies and/or any of the several businesses with which we work, we lose control over how they will use, collect, and/or disseminate your information. While we expect that they will not use that information other than as described herein, you understand and agree that MeetingBurner is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these others, and you agree that MeetingBurner is not responsible for how such information is ultimately used.

**Third Party Intermediaries**  
We may use a credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies only use your information for billing purposes and, to the extent they store your credit card or other private financial information, do so in a secure industry-standard fashion.

**Service Providers**  
We partner with other third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services and for purposes referenced in their privacy policies.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event MeetingBurner goes through a significant business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a major portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. MeetingBurner will strive to notify users via email prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information, consistent with our notification of changes section.  
**Legal Proceedings**  
We may be required by law to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe instructions sent with every email. 

Users who wish to remove cookies may do so by following directions provided in their internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of the site may be limited.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that MeetingBurner is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the young is important to us. If you are not 18 years old you are not permitted to access this website for any reason. Because of this, we never knowingly collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 18.

**Telecommunications Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of your telecommunications information is important to us. When users make phone calls to or from telecommunication services provided by us, we may track information about the name, phone number, and other information about the call. We do not share this information, unless required to do so by law. We may use this information in the aggregate to analyze trends or to improve the service. By contacting us via telephone you are allowing us to contact you even if your phone number is on any legal DNC (do not call) lists. 

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, we strive to ensure that their information is protected both online and off-line. However, please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. In addition, we cannot guarantee the privacy of information that you choose to share through the MeetingBurner software; for example, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number and/or a social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with industry-standard technology.

While we use industry-standard technology to protect sensitive information online, we also work to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a secure facility.

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users, it may be necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), if a user no longer wishes to use our service, or otherwise wishes to review the user's personally identifiable information, a user may review, correct, update, or delete/deactivate the user's personally identifiable information by logging in to the user's account.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places that we deem appropriate. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

support@meetingburner.com  
www.meetingburner.com 

This policy is effective August 13, 2015
